do-follow.info 2012-06-11

# Privacy Policy | DoFollow , DoFollow Blog Directory , Social Bookmarking , Forums , Article Directories DoFollow Sites

**What information do we collect?**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

If you attempt to become a Client or otherwise choose to provide information to us, this website shall collect Personal Information from you. This information includes: name and email. Once collected, we will store your information for a reasonable period of time for record keeping purposes. The information we store is deleted as space requires or in the normal course of business.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

info@do-follow.info

News Articles - DoFollow web news - News Articles on Business, Entertainment, Technology, Ecommerce & more ,Free add url DoFollow,DoFollow site deployment,DoFollow Blog Directory,Social Bookmarking,Article Directories
